Guide to the WCSU Office of University Publications & Design Records RG 7.3.2 RG 7.3.2
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Photographs
  - University Photographer's photo archive
    - CDs - Oct 2005-Dec 2005 (Box psa_55)
      Contains: 68 envelopes. Topics: 'Amahl"; conflict resolution class; One Acts; candids; symphony orchestra; jazz drummer masterclass; Latino forum; vietnam exhibit; New York Times; Great American Smoke-out; Connecticut Choral Society scholarships; debate team; social work gala; ConnCap; psychology club; JetBlue; international week; women's basketball; wine tasting; Vets Program; science at night; he-said she-said: A Choices Performance; BlackHawk Helicopter; symphonic and wind ensemble; Keyboard club; day of the dead; HPX: Russian aids workers; BashBish Falls; Haunted Hay rides; social work honor society; dream week alpha delta pi; premier financial services; Dr. Chris Martine: Evolution of separate sexes in plants; alcohol awareness week; DUI demo; homecoming; mentoring department cookout; women's basketball; etiquette dinner; J.R. Roach library award; holistic event; Hispanic heritage month; men's hockey
    - CDs - Jan 2006-Apr 2006 (Box psa_56)
      Contains: 62 envelopes. Topics: OWLs (non-traditional students); men's lacrosse; women's lacrosse; men's basketball; freedom live; nursing tea; under-age drinking; chamber of commerce Hispanic business seminar; women's history month; sculpting class; music alumni event; Danbury Hospital Children's Day; Hispanic Leadership Conference for high school students; "As You Like It"; women's conference; president initiative program; "Step Into the World": trip to the UN; yearbook photos; diversity program; phonathon; National Collegiate Hispanic Honor Society; Ugandan music; NSCS book drive; snow; silo; fresh start scholarship; tutoring lab; African film festival; afro-peruvian jazz masterclass; meet the Wallabies; science seminar; WestConn Society Luncheon; MLK tribute; legislators visit; alumni board holiday dinner; MFA
    - CDs - Jan 2006-Apr 2006 (Box psa_57)
      Contains: 29 envelopes. Topics: alumni cocktail party; jazz fest; Barnard Awards; Jane Goodall at O'Neill Center; Heidi Chronicles; softball Alicia O'Brien's 400th win; Wizard of Oz; West Lake Cleanup; Tartan Day; career fair; percussion concert; men's lacrosse; Danbury Hospital Children's Day; Hispanic leadership conference for high school students; ARM program (Alcohol awareness); St Patrick's Day; "As You Like It"; women's basketball; women's soccer; men's basketball; Connecticut State-wide healthy campus initiative; "I Would Forgive You..."
    - CDs - Apr 2006-Jun 2006 (Box psa_58)
      Contains: 70 envelopes. Topics: Staff candids; RCU 3rd birthday; Betty Ann Madeiros mural; president's club cocktail party; Rotary club; "Day in the life"; women's soccer; math enrichment program; Norwalk Hospital; German program; Ives Anderson Mural; graduate student awards; nursing; Katrina relief; men's baseball; writer's conference weekend; psychology journal luncheon; Cinco de Mayo; alumni scholarship dinner; Dr. Schmotter guest DJ at WXCI; Tai Chi universal day; Jazz fest clinics; ANIfest; Choices DUI program; Goodall Symposium; Goodall Summit; Social Work senior project; Nursing honor society; academic day; Roots and Shoots; president's scholarship; photography masterclass; new york botanical gardens; graduate profiles; diversity at university; united diversified consultation company; Cendent Mobility; film fest; Cambridge debate
    - CDs - Jun 2006-Oct 2006 (Box psa_59)
      Contains: 67 envelopes. Topics: Hispanic heritage; choices; Chinese visit; tri-state weather conference; golden circle luncheon; National Guard; theater workshop; Manhattan string quartet; haunted history; magnet school; genome debate; banned books; childcare center; teddy bear clinic; solar viewing; WestConn Day; alumni board; Choices barbecue; Taste of Danbury; social science; softball fundraiser; talent show at Ives park; MFA writing; dorm shots; debate camp; ceramics class; band camp performance; parking garage construction; UCDA submissions; German students visit BI (Boehringer Ingelheim?) headquarters
    - CDs - May 2006-Aug 2006 (Box psa_60)
      Contains: 26 envelopes. Topics: graduation; university ball; student leadership; Puerto Rico; football practice; offensive meeting; police department awards; MFA writing; alumni golf; music camp; WestComm institute for science teacher research (WISTR); candids; orientation; Rosetta Stone (software program); ConnCap; Heidi Chronicles NYC; WRD: Student Research Day; Rugby
    - CDs - Sep 2006-Oct 2006 (Box psa_61)
      Contains: 23 envelopes. Topics: women's tennis;football; marching band; orchestra rehearsal; board of trustees; career development center interview workshop; women's volleyball; marketing shots; women's soccer; men's rugby; men's soccer; football; mock chemical accident
    - CDs - Oct 2006-Dec 2006 (Box psa_62)
      Contains: 42 envelopes. Topics: alumni marketplace; WestConn Wear; psychology day; foundation board; legislator breakfast; women's soccer; jazz clinic; magic show; "Amahl"; concert choir; Japanese Noh dance; symphonic band; wine tasting; election day; teaching American history; multicultural conference for future teachers; "Full Monty"; childcare center; rethinking American History in a global age; roots and shoots; mediation; art; lacrosse; class of 1961; music scholarship; German studies; research day; folk life project
    - CDs - Oct 2006-Dec 2006 (Box psa_63)
      Contains: 27 envelopes. Topics: holiday jazz; men's ice hockey; president & provost visit; men's basketball; women's soccer; football; student athlete scholarship presentation; student polls; Hispanic heritage; Danbury garden club; "Full Monty"; women's lacrosse; octoberfest; jazz; China forum; tutoring workshop; Hord Academy; homecoming; Carter inauguration; etiquette dinner; bird poop in White street garage
    - CDs - Jan 2007-Mar 2007 (Box psa_64)
      Contains: 62 envelopes. Topics: Bronx Zoo; softball; men's lacrosse; baseball; Bethel Middle School Science Fair; grad profiles; women's history month; Mahendra University Visit; Caraluzzi Scholars; Choices: "Can I Kiss You?"; international student luncheon; alumni dinner; science at night; health fair; women's center; Choices; David Pease from Miami Dolphins; observatory viewing; keyboard club; Dominican Education Initiative; Onassic Cultural center; Romeo & Juliet; planetarium; Mozart scholarship; economic impact press conference; clubs carnival; snow; women's basketball; magnet school; alumni marketplace; student profiles; MFA writing
    - CDs - Jan 2007-Apr 2007 (Box psa_65)
      Contains: 24 envelopes. Topics: Chinese students; Pirates of Penzance; Trail by Jury; grad profiles; debate team; CSU day; WestConn Society Luncheon; Haas library illuminata; Romeo & Juliet; immigration forum; national science foundation; cabaret; men's basketball; "colored museum" production; Red Cross blood drive; said & meant: dress rehearsal; WSCS ribbon cutting; women's basketball; bridge program; RAD training
    - CDs - Apr 2007-Aug 2007 (Box psa_66)
      Contains: 68 envelopes. Topics: student profile; grad profiles; new faculty (anthropology); Underage drinking; Potterfest; Harry Potter; music camp; MFA writing; "Sisterhood of the Traveling Pants"; Romeo & Juliet; Joe Namath; German Students visit city hall; orientation; Rotary club scholarships; retirement party; WRD research day; puppets; athletic banquet; WISTR; child abuse conference; student leadership banquet; child advocacy conference; holistic health fair; CSU day; TKE jumpathon; Alzheimer's association; Choices carnival; WXCI; baseball; men's rugby; women's lacrosse; emeriti luncheon; alumni scholarship; earth day; roots and shoots; ANIFest; employee-alumni luncheon; Amy Chin & Melanie Belec: Nursing Scholarship; flooding from nor'easter; grad profiles; herpetology; social sciences alumni event; nursing honor society; oral history project; music alumni reception; women's lacrosse
    - CDs - Feb 2007-Jun 2007 (Box psa_67)
      Contains: 21 envelopes. Topics: orientation; Danbury History Comes Alive; commencement; "Iphigenia" the show; psychology day; university ball; SIAS; opera; jazz fest; grad profiles; roots & shoots; Barnard Awards; Cartus Alumni event; DUI awareness; Dr Zeng; softball; men's tennis; men's lacrosse; Dominican literacy project; Connecticut small business and minority showcase
    - CDs - Jun 2006-Oct 2007 (Box psa_68)
      Contains: 24 envelopes. Topics: homecoming; athletic hall of fame; jazz faculty concert; "Cherry Orchard" (play); football; Ives family fair; women's soccer; childcare center 10th anniversary; men's rugby; volleyball; Ives Concert Park; clubs carnival; Newman Center barbecue; aerial images; Conncap; "Sisterhood of the Traveling Pants"; Joe Namath football camp; viewbook; dance team
    - CDs - Aug 2007-Dec 2007 (Box psa_69)
      Contains: 57 envelopes. Topics: Christmas show; snow; CSU backpack; women's soccer; NCAA soccer; music; president's community forum; patriotic cows; stem cell lecture by Laura Grabel; rotary club meeting; mock robbery; accounting career forum; wine tasting; Caraluzzi Scholarship; Halloween; men's ice hockey; Joe Shaboo: Shalamazoo; women's center: stop the violence; Ives Park disrepair; chemistry wizards; candids; Rona's origami project; homecoming; APIC dinner; alumni golf; banned books; Ulysses; light the night; leukemia; Roots & Shoots; nursing community breakfast; Hord Foundation; Field hockey; Centennial scholarship; wiffle ball; SPS luncheon
    - CDs - Oct 2007-Dec 2007 (Box psa_70)
      Contains: 21 envelopes. Topics: women's basketball; vanguard jazz orchestra; children's Christmas show; men's basketball; women's soccer; men's ice hockey; international education week; SPS distant alumni program; men's soccer; football; Halloween; solar viewing; "What kind of America are we?"; "Cherry Orchard" (play); celebration of dance; K. Logan Scholarship; Rona's origamic project; executive forum 10th anniversary; wine & cheese party; women's field hockey
    - CDs - Jan 2008-Apr 2008 (Box psa_71)
      Contains: 50 envelopes. Topics: Ancell School accreditation breakfast; Choices DUI awareness; Roots and Shoots; minority students; grad profiles; alumni scholarship dinner; spring opera "Suor Angelica"; Sigma Theta Tau consortium; "Stole" (play); DMC Russian Soul & Art Show; St Patrick's Day; Dala Shore; Danbury's History: women; nursing career fair; women's history month; "RecFest" at the O'Neill Center; legislative breakfast; Barnard Awards; black history month; Hispanic grant enrollment; global warming program; national mentoring day; merit awards luncheon
    - CDs - Jan 2008-Apr 2008 (Box psa_72)
      Contains: 24 envelopes. Topics: Ancell Alumni reception; ice hockey fund raising; women's lacrosse; men's tennis; baseball; CSU Day; men's lacrosse; cabaret; Board of Trustees meeting; grad profiles; diversity @ university; Ives Concert Park; Dance: Brazil capoeira; career fair @ O'Neill center; women's softball; meteorology; debate a debater for $2; women's history month; women's basketball; "Tommy" (play); WXCI; history department bake sale; spirit band; men's basketball; MLK Day; literary fest
    - CDs - Apr 2008-Sep 2008 (Box psa_73)
      Contains: 46 envelopes. Topics: 9/11; Fr Peter: Layola College; Inspired Images (art show); women's soccer; Henry Moore (sculptor); "Sisterhood of the Traveling Pants 2"; soccer camp; ConnCap; YMCA; Shalamazoo; Ives; lacrosse camp; heart and brain disection; puppetpalooza; Joe Namath; president to president scholarship; Congressman Chris Murphy; orientation; police explorers; MFA; alumni marketplace; CT Film Festival; grad profiles; WRD research day; JLA Mock Trial; Chinese Honor Society; Roots and Shoots; Barnard Award; senior art thesis show; Ancell Convocation; psychology research journal
    - CDs - Apr 2008-Jun 2008 (Box psa_74)
      Contains: 20 envelopes. Topics: German students; SVPA building; grad profiles; WISTR; commencement; athletics awards banquet; Ball (venue shots); men's lacrosse; nursing society reception; Jazzfest clinics; world tai chi day; jazzfest; "Take your sons and daughters to work day"; Choices: ice cream sundaes alcohol awareness event; Greeks do Earth Day campus cleanup
    - CDs - Jun 2008-Aug 2008 (Box psa_75)
      Contains: 15 envelopes. Topics: lit fest; animation camp; athletics; diving; nutmeg games; swimming; rugby; archery; martial arts; skydivers; red bull motocross; National Guard employer award; band camp; softball; fast pitch softball; string camp; Joe Namath football camp; education connection; orientation
    - CDs - Aug 2008-Oct 2008 (Box psa_76)
      Contains: 21 envelopes. Topics: Ives Family Fair; women's tennis; ice hockey; banned book readathon; president's scholarship; alumni golf; men's soccer; football; cabaret; international language panel; science research seminar; women's field hockey; NYC dinner cruise; men's rugby; women's volleyball; Connecticut Film Festival press conference; golden circle luncheon; club candids; move-in day; orientation for international students; president's faculty picnic; MFA writing; lit fest
    - CDs - Sep 2008-Oct 2008 (Box psa_77)
      Contains: 40 envelopes. Topics: Commuter Van; Presidential Debate; Young Republicans, Cafe/students; Health Fair; Maggie Astrup; Homecoming; Cheerleaders; Dance Team; King/Queen; Alumni Reunion; Sigma Ki Alumni Rugby; APICS; Scholarship ceremony; Student Doner Reception; Road Scholars Don Gagnon; Hist. Dept.; 2008 Election; Student Center; One book Event; Westside Campus History; Etiquette Dinner CDC; Shawn Obrien; Marci Delcourt; Abby Zink; Bryan Samuels; Physics Lab Equipment; Ice Hockey; Campus Shots; Brian Stevens; Nancy Bayton; Ron Mason; Bill Hawkins; Mark Hasskarl; Tom Edson; Voter Registration; L Rinker; A Manes; D. Costello; Laura teilman; MFA; Joe Mingachos; Bill Glass; Banned books; Banned Book Debate; Holocaust; NYC; Jessica Taibeault; Andrew Schneider; International Recruitment; Choices; Alcohol Awareness; Alumni Golf; Men's Soccer; Darius Rejali; Accessibility Services Staff; Power Outage; Classes Outside; Republican Student Group with Politicians; Haas Archives Record Collection; Darla Shaw; John Farrell; Housing Photos; Women's Rugby; URI; Women's Tennis; UMASS Dartmouth; Marketing Class; Psychology lecture Series; Dr. Joshua Aronson; Liz Popiel; Beth Morrison; Dawn Fletcher; Birte Selvaraj; D. Dennis; Music; Manhattan Strings; Diversity lecture; Free-thinking Immigration; Friar Peter and Rinker; Philosophy Day; Bryan Samuel; Philanthropy Day; "Cemetery Club" (play); Hossen; Football; Albright.
    - CDs - Sep 2008-Dec 2008 (Box psa_78)
      Contains: 30 envelopes. Topics: Snow; Faculty Promotion/Tenure; Student center Renovations; Marci Delcourt; Faculty recognition; MFA Art Judy Glantzmann; Velvet Ritch; Dorothy Day; Rufus Reid Masterclass; HPX Fair; X-mas Show Poster; Clothesline Project; Litchfield Hall Renovations; Symphonic Band; Hancock Student Leaders; Alumni Event; German Studies; Arion Singing Society; "The Singing Revolution about Estonia's Independence"; Admissions; Cartus Art on Loan Program; Dr. Hineline; CSU 25th Anniv.; Fairfield Dorm Rooms; Hist. Dept. Faculty; Peter Schumond Puppeteer; Jane Goodall; Alumni Dinner Theater; Locks of Love; Social Sciences Alumni Event; David Straut President Scholar Recipient; Wine-Tasting; Ung Diversity Lecture; "First They Killed My father" Lecture by Luong Ung; Nursing Presentation; Day of the Dead; Deans' and Chairs' Lunch; Murphy/Capiello Senate Debate; One Book Diwali Celebration; Daria Shaw; Fruits and Shoots; Dr. Rosemarie - Morgan/Thomas Hardy Scholar; Bryan Samuels.
    - CDs - Oct 2008-Dec 2008 (Box psa_79)
      Contains: 20 envelopes. Topics: Dan Goble AR; Amahl Dress Rehersal; Saint Thomas Students; Norton Mezvinzky; Music Videos; DFD Swearing in, City Hall; Jimmy Johnson Fire Marshall; "A X-mas carol" (Play); Chemistry Wizards; Karen Cody Cooper; Concert Choir; Union x-mas Party Committee; CSUS 25th Anniv. Celeb. at Capitol; Vet. day program; Women's LEC Championship Soccer; Football V. College of NJ; LAC Semi FInal UMASS; Volleyball V. Plymouth; Cabaret; Fire Dept. Growth Training; Debate Tournament; Cabaret Set; Diwali; Education Conf. with Susan Bysiewicz; Anna Quindlir; Tom Lonergan; Dr. Yen; 5k Run; Campus to Campus; Homecoming; tea and Fashion Show; Walter bernstein; Alumni art Show; Donar Student Recpt.; Convocation; SAS & ASV.
    - CDs - Jan 2009-Apr 2009 (Box psa_80)
      Contains: 53 envelopes. Topics: Stephen Price; Steve Roberts; Linda Cahill; MFA Senior Thesis; Choices; Grad History Club "Wealthy free Women of Color"; bear Mt. GPS; Alex Standish; Andy Oguma; One Book one community; Mira Nair; WCSU Society Luncheon; John Azzaetti; Rich Ashe; ESPN; Don Gagnon; Wynn-Wilcox; Politicians at WCSU; Roberts Avenue School; Men's Lacrosse; WHM; "Kiss a pig" Habitat for Humanity; Tutoring; Broadview Middle School; Psych. Students; Swimming; Francesca Testa; John Ready; Women's Lacrosse; Linda Plecity; Jason Hancock; Najah Mahfoud; Sname Wilson; Laura Telman; Adam Radzimirski; HTC; Packing for Cape Verde Trip; MSQ; Fashion Forward; MTV Casting; SBDC Entrepreneur Workshop; Laurel Halloran; WXCI 36th Reunion; Jill Cook; Swimming; Jazz Concert; Orchestra; Jazz Big band Concert; Orchestra Rehearsal; Eric Lewis Conductor & Miles?; Peace Deputy Secretary General Stein; Villum Stad; Nursing; Karen Daley; Herbert Wright; Dance team; Gymnastics; Chris Murphy; Opera headshots; Figiero; "the tempest"; Basketball; Sax & Piano Albert Regni, Alan farnham; Russ Hirschfield; Scholarship; Crystal Schewe; Josh Stanley; MFA Artwork; Women's Basketball; Diving; Tammy Hammershoy; Pres. Inauguration; MLK day; Ruby Dee; Farooq Kathwari; HSLP; Jonathan Soares.
    - CDs - Jan 2009-Mar 2009 (Box psa_81)
      Contains: 19 envelopes. Topics: 'Proof"; Theater Dept.; Brianne Chasonoff; Pauling Elementary School; Men's basketball; Fire Dept. New Street Fire; WHM; Women's Lacrosse; Barnard; Meredith Loberto; Nursing; Karen Daley; laurel Halloran; James Furman; Piano Class; "The Tempest" (Play); Bridgeport Police Dept.; Andres Arrizo; Adam Radzimierski; Women"s Basketball; Harlem Globetrotters; Nursing; Bridge/Stem program; Roots and Shoots; Dr. Buster Soaries; B. Perretti; Richard Halburton; Water rescue Exercise; Dod/Murphy Forum at WCSU; Protesters; College Republicans.
    - CDs - Mar 2009-Apr 2009 (Box psa_82)
      Contains: 20 envelopes. Topics: Quad Party; Lyme Disease; PE Class; Jarod Cowden; Domatilia Pereira; Choices; Kids on Campus; Women's Lacrosse, Men's Lacrosse, Softball; Weather Conference; Dr. marc Goldstein; Veteran's Issues; Relay for life; Derek Leka; Intl. Students for Missy Gluckmann with Rob Wittemore; Barnard Awards; take your sons and daughters to work day; "Marriage of Figaro" (Play); Men's Tennis; Westside SGA Boating in WSCC; baseball; Poetry reading; Downtown Danbury; Bill Eppridge; SGA Elections; Egg Hunt; Stephen Price; Sname Wilson; Najah Mahfoud; Meredith Liberto; Jeff Sphunt; Career Fair; John Farrel; Women's Lacrosse; Susan Krauss Whitbourne; Bethel Middleschool Science Fair; Sibling Weekend; NCATE Education Fair and Dinner.
    - CDs - Apr 2009-Jul 2009 (Box psa_83)
      Contains: 47 envelopes. Topics: Tony Cirone; Rick Bassett; Alumni Barbeque; Roberts Avenue School; Jeff Sphunt; "Bridges"; Band Camp; Bruny Edberts; Steve Goetsch; Caroline Lanier; Irene Sherlock; CT Bio Bus; German Students; Namath Camp; Archaeology Labwork; Weeville Survival; Theater Posters; Adventures of Reynard the Fox (Play); Joseph Hayman and Adele Scholarship; M. Portnow's Painting; Brian Bielefeldt; Graduation Ceremony; Alumni Spring Weekend; Humanitarian Club; Kate Birdeye Presentation; Karen Koza's Marketing Class; Nick Bussett; USB Clock; Stephanie Merzy; Kym Powe; Becca Mage; Tony Zat Zick; MFA; Andy Rogers; Juanita Curtis; Anthony DePoto; Dave Halek; Dan Castello; Mock Trial; Nursing; Senior Group Photo; Elizabeth Fisher; Army Commissioning with Mjr. garcia US Army; Jason Burger; Macricosta's lecture Series; Joseph Platano-Entrepreneur of the Year; Drop-kick Murphys; Cristina Kalafut; Frank Beaudery; Samantha Tuozzulo; Jim Minneff Tree Dedication; Buildings; parking garage; Who's Who Student leadership Dinner; Brianne Chasonaff; Charles Alexander; Athletic Banquet; Convocation; Ancell Awards; Jazz fest; Nursing and Management Dinner; TKE Jumpathon; Earth Day; roots and Shoots; Hist. Students; Clio Publication; piano Recittal; Percussion Ensemble; Asian Photogallery; Childcare Cabaret; SGA Elections; Symposium on Homelessness; Veterans' Writing Workshop; Anthony Swofford; DIversity lecture; Kenji Yoshino; Chinese Culture Lunch; Grad Open House.
    - CDs - Apr 2009-Jun 2009 (Box psa_84)
      Contains: 19 envelopes. Topics: Archaeology Sitework; Winestein & Morrison; Candlewood Lake; Weavles/Environment Science; MFA Art Show NYC; Young's Event for SVPA; CT Film festival Workshops; Undergrad Commencement; Grad Commencement; WRD Research Day; Dr. Ana Ribeiro; Stephanie Ardizzone; Multicultural fair; Psych Journal Luncheon & Scholar Journal; SGA/PAC; Alumni Nurses Reception; SPS Convocation; Jeff Sphunt; Charles Price; Morten & Coza; University Ball; Jazz fest; Danilo Perez Trio; Social Work Faculty; Art Show.
    - CDs - Jun 2009-Aug 2009 (Box psa_85)
      Contains: 18 envelopes. Topics: Young People's Writing Conference; nutmeg games; Willie Knight camp; Band Camp Carnival; supper youth college fair; Ives Concert Park: Fine Arts Series; Green Light Camp; Campus exteriors; lacrosse camp; Candlewood Lake research; string camp; Danbury Fire Department community day; Reynard the Fox; Connecticut Science Center; Namath camp; Bill Hawkins; Orientation
    - CDs - Aug 2009-Oct 2009 (Box psa_86)
      Contains: 43 envelopes. Topics: Campus shots; tennis; class of 1959 50th Reunion; football; dance team; reunions; homecoming; hall of fame; Tres Vidas performance; Hispanic Cultural Awareness Month; MFA Art; Health Fair; Childcare center; scholarship reception ceremony; Connecticut Consortium for Law and Citizenship Education; LAX Alumni Games; Lacrosse Team Candids; Men's ice hockey; men's rugby; field hockey; international education conference; one book one community; substance abuse conference; retirement reception; HVCA Awards Breakfast; Candlewood Lake Authority; Larry Marsicano; Volleyball; tailgating; women's rugby; Jackie and Sean's wedding; Women's Tennis; Field Hockey; Men's soccer; young writer's conference; president's club reception; OBOC event; Baseball alumni game; women's center walk against violence; banned books; Trojan women: Greek theater; dean's list dinner; DFD medical response; Danbury fire department; City of Angels (play); Clubs carnival; campus shots; MFA young writers conference
    - CDs - Aug 2009-Sep 2009 (Box psa_87)
      Contains: 19 envelopes. Topics: golden circle luncheon; constitution day debate; women's tennis; New York City cruise; field hockey; Steve Neuwirth lecture; women's soccer; volleyball; men's soccer; clubs carnival; Great Hollow Day Program; Ives Blues Fest; The Tempest; Sinatra fund raiser; Candlewood Lake Weevil Project
    - CDs - Sep 2009-Dec 2009 (Box psa_88)
      Contains: 35 envelopes. Topics: fireworks; MFA poetry; "A Flea in Her Ear": detail shots; Candlewood lake water forum; science at night; Jazz with John Schofield; HSLP Cohort 1; Bridge Program; Meteorology; Stress Fair; nursing job fair; renovation; choir concert; jazz; ochestra concert; "Amahl"(play); faculty art show; morning glory breakfast; lacrosse; senior day; Hat City debates; JLA club; students rights and responsibilities panel; Mary Edgetts 107th Birthday; Morganti Donation; Volleyball; men's soccer; Field Hockey